[Music]
if we're gonna take the dead
together we will pull each other
excuse me my name is patchBell I was
told that a friend of mine was badly her
and was brought here a few days ago his
name is concho may
and he's one of my best friends I need
to know if he's okay
it looks like somebody named kancho may
checked himself
into the hospital last week if you want
to pay that sexy baby a visit he's in
the last room down the hall
please don't take very long ago visiting
hours will be over in about 10 minutes
thank you miss we won't take long let's
go zach
do you think kanto maze hurt badly I'm
worried about him did he mention what
exactly happened to him
i hope polgori didn't beat him with that
baseball bat again
kyo keo are you listening to me oh
i get it you're so lost in your own
grief that you're at lost forwards
it's okay that's normal I think
that [ __ ] said the room at the end of
the hall right well let's go one image
how have you been it's me your best
buddy fat Bell
do you hear me we would have gotten here
sooner but we had to stop by walmart on
the way here
so I could go inside and poop kayo
something's wrong kuncho made won't
respond to anything I say
something about this doesn't feel right
you would think
that if konchome was really hurt falgore
would want to be here with him
in the hospital it's a shame that keo
has to be here right now
if he wasn't here I could have sex with
this [ __ ] doc baby
and since he would be unconscious nobody
would ever know
way you [ __ ] let go of him I said
[ __ ] let go of him
what the who the [ __ ] are you three
[ __ ] supposed to be what's going on
here
hey I recognize you you're you're rooney
doodle
lead singer of the famous doodlebops
quickly that's why
we've got to get out of here hurry
that's why come on
if you don't come over here you're gonna
be [ __ ] in the ass
hooray you don't have much time
we have to go now
we'll rape you it's okay
I'm a friend of the Sonic Underground
I'm batman [ __ ] I told you guys that
oversized bat was following us ever
since we entered the hospital
let's go zach
we are out of here hold on to your [ __ ]
what are you all just standing around
for shoot him
shoot him in his cute tight butt
no they got away damn it damn it
somebody is going to pay for this